Ngày xưa em đã nói em thương anh nhất mà
Once upon a time, I said I loved you the most
Ngày xưa em cũng nói yêu anh cho đến già
Once upon a time, I said I would love you until I was old
Mà giờ đây em đã thương thêm ai nữa à?
But now you love someone else?
Có lẽ bây giờ em muốn ta rời xa
Maybe now you want me to leave
Anh cũng đã từng nghĩ rằng em coi anh là tất cả
I also used to think that you considered me everything
Nhưng sao hôm nay anh mới nhận ra là
But why did I just realize today?
Em đã có thêm một người, một người thứ hai
I have another person, a second person
Và em buông lời nói chúng ta nên dừng lại
And I said we should stop
Em ơi anh làm gì sai sao em nỡ buông câu dừng lại?
Honey, what did I do wrong? Why did you say stop?
Em ơi anh làm gì sai sao em yêu thêm người thứ hai?
Honey, what did I do wrong? Why do you love a second person?
Anh thương em thật lòng đấy sao em không thương anh thật lòng?
I really love you, why don't you really love me?
Tình cảm đó em coi là số không
I consider that love as zero
Nếu anh đã làm gì sai thì xin em nói
If I did anything wrong, please tell me
Em nói đi em sao cứ im lặng?
Tell me, why are you staying silent?
Tình mình bao lâu, nay hóa thành tro tàn
Our love for so long has now turned into ashes
Đớn đau này anh gánh hạnh phúc còn lại nhường em
I will bear this pain and leave the rest to you
(Chẳng lẽ yêu em là sai, chẳng anh yêu vậy sao)
(Is it wrong to love you? Isn't that how you love me)
(Vốn dĩ yêu thương một ai là anh không thấu)
(In fact, when you love someone, you don't understand)
Anh cũng đã từng nghĩ rằng em coi anh là tất cả
I also used to think that you considered me everything
Nhưng sao hôm nay anh mới nhận ra là
But why did I just realize today?
Em đã có thêm một người, một người thứ hai
I have another person, a second person
Và em buông lời nói chúng ta nên dừng lại
And I said we should stop
Em ơi anh làm gì sai sao em nỡ buông câu dừng lại?
Honey, what did I do wrong? Why did you say stop?
Em ơi anh làm gì sai sao em yêu thêm người thứ hai?
Honey, what did I do wrong? Why do you love a second person?
Anh thương em thật lòng đấy sao em không thương anh thật lòng?
I really love you, why don't you really love me?
Tình cảm đó em coi là số không
I consider that love as zero
Nếu anh đã làm gì sai thì xin em nói
If I did anything wrong, please tell me
Em nói đi em sao cứ im lặng?
Tell me, why are you staying silent?
Tình mình bao lâu, nay hóa thành tro tàn
Our love for so long has now turned into ashes
Đớn đau này anh gánh hạnh phúc còn lại nhường em
I will bear this pain and leave the rest to you
Em ơi anh làm gì sai sao em nỡ buông câu dừng lại?
Honey, what did I do wrong? Why did you say stop?
Em ơi anh làm gì sai sao em yêu thêm người thứ hai?
Honey, what did I do wrong? Why do you love a second person?
Anh thương em thật lòng đấy sao em không thương anh thật lòng?
I really love you, why don't you really love me?
Tình cảm đó em coi là số không
I consider that love as zero
Nếu anh đã làm gì sai thì xin em nói
If I did anything wrong, please tell me
Em nói đi em sao cứ im lặng
Tell me, why do you keep silent?
Tình mình bao lâu, nay hóa thành tro tàn
Our love for so long has now turned into ashes
Đớn đau này anh gánh hạnh phúc còn lại nhường em
I will bear this pain and leave the rest to you